freejinger.org 2019-11-05

# Privacy Policy - Free Jinger

_**Free Jinger Privacy Policy**_

**Registration**

Some basic personal information is required in order to register with FreeJinger: 

* Email Address - By providing your email address, you can receive messages via your existing email account. You have the option to have this information hidden or available to other board members. 

* User Name - This is how you are identified when you participate in forums. While many other aspects of your account. like your avatar, can be updated at will, your user name cannot be changed. 

**Information FreeJinger Requests**

Free Jinger uses outside ad companies to display ads on its sites. These ads may contain cookies and Free Jinger may not have access to this information. 

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

No children under 18 are allowed to participate in Free Jinger. 

**Participation**

The above describes information that is provided “actively” - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join Free Jinger, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided “passively” - meaning, that Free Jinger obtains this information when you login to your account. This is done primarily through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are used to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a ‘members-only’ area, your browser’s cookie file is checked to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you’re taken to the page that you have requested. If not, you’ll be directed to the login screen, where you can login to your account, or register if you are not yet a member. Cookies are also used in conjunction with some ad banners to determine their effectiveness. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that many Web sites write through your browser when you visit them. A cookie can only be read by the site that places it, so we can’t track your browsing history based on any other cookies in your browser. Most browsers also allow the option of displaying a warning before accepting a cookie, or refusing all cookies. 

**Advertising**

Free Jinger uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number are not shared with advertisers without you “clicking through” and providing it yourself. 

The third-party advertising companies presently utilized are Google AdSense, amazon.com and Chitika. Please read [Google Adsense privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/), [Chitika privacy policy](http://chitika.com/privacy) and [Amazon.com privacy policy](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496). 

Free Jinger LLC is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. 

**Public Forums**

Free Jinger is a public message board. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in such a public forum becomes public information. In addition, information that is disclosed in private forums such as a private message may be disclosed by the recipient. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Individual posters maintain a copyright on any copyrighted original material that individual posts, to the extent allowed by law. Freejinger.org will not sell, distribute, or repost on another internet entity not owned or controlled by Free Jinger LLC any posts made on FreeJinger.org. 

**Disclosures**

We may disclose Personal Data without providing you with a choice under the following limited circumstances to: (1) protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (2) enforce our Terms of Service; or (3) comply with the law or legal process. 

**Security**

Free Jinger is housed on servers maintained and operated by Liquid Web. Liquid Web utilizes security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. Servers have security in place to guard against an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users. 

If you feel this policy has been violated, [please contact us](mailto:helpme@freejinger.org). 

**Termination**

Account deletion is not permitted. 

**Summary**

Post personal information with caution. Anything posted on Free Jinger may be quoted by another user on site and possibly offsite. When in doubt remember THE INTERNET IS FOREVER! 

### Third Parties

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

**Spam Defense**

The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.

**reCAPTCHA V2**

This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.
